<CALLOUT>
    <CALLOUTMESSAGE>Package Theft</CALLOUTMESSAGE>
    <CALLOUTADVISORY>Officer for Area Surveillance required</CALLOUTADVISORY>
    <TASK>There have been several package thefts reported in {ZoneName}. Drive to the area and stay alert.</TASK>
    <D_FriendlyPostman>
        <DIALOGUE>~y~You~s~: Good afternoon, sir. Mind if I have a word with you real quick?</DIALOGUE>
        <DIALOGUE>~o~Postman~s~: Sure thing, officer. Is there a problem?</DIALOGUE>
        <DIALOGUE>~y~You~s~: Not exactly. We’ve had a few incidents in this neighborhood involving stolen packages. I just saw you drop one off and wanted to check everything's in order.</DIALOGUE>
        <DIALOGUE>~o~Postman~s~: Ah, yeah. I totally get that. I've actually heard some neighbors mention weird stuff going on.</DIALOGUE>
        <DIALOGUE>~y~You~s~: Can I ask what delivery company you’re working for and what address that package was meant for?</DIALOGUE>
        <DIALOGUE>~o~Postman~s~: I'm with GoPostal. The package was for number 123 Grove Street – just a small box. I even left it at the porch and took a photo.</DIALOGUE>
        <DIALOGUE>~y~You~s~: Alright, sounds good. Just doing our due diligence. Thanks for being so cooperative.</DIALOGUE>
        <DIALOGUE>~o~Postman~s~: No problem at all. Better safe than sorry.</DIALOGUE>
        <DIALOGUE>~y~You~s~: You're good to go. Drive safe.</DIALOGUE>
        <DIALOGUE>~o~Postman~s~: Will do. Appreciate you checking in, officer. Stay safe out there.</DIALOGUE>
    </D_FriendlyPostman>
    <D_AnnoyedPostman>
        <DIALOGUE>~y~You~s~: Hi there. I need a moment of your time, if that’s okay.</DIALOGUE>
        <DIALOGUE>~o~Postman~s~: I mean… yeah, I guess. What’s this about?</DIALOGUE>
        <DIALOGUE>~y~You~s~: We’ve had a few reports of fake delivery drivers stealing packages in this area. Just wanted to verify your delivery.</DIALOGUE>
        <DIALOGUE>~o~Postman~s~: You’ve got to be kidding me. I’ve got 40 more stops to make.</DIALOGUE>
        <DIALOGUE>~y~You~s~: I understand. I just need to confirm where you dropped that last package and who you work for.</DIALOGUE>
        <DIALOGUE>~o~Postman~s~: It was 119 Grove Street. Small box, signed "J. Ramirez" on the manifest. I left it near the door.</DIALOGUE>
        <DIALOGUE>~y~You~s~: Got it. Do you have any ID or badge I can take a quick look at?</DIALOGUE>
        <DIALOGUE>~o~Postman~s~: Yeah, yeah, one sec. *[hands ID]* Here you go.</DIALOGUE>
        <DIALOGUE>~y~You~s~: Thanks. That checks out. Appreciate your time.</DIALOGUE>
        <DIALOGUE>~o~Postman~s~: Alright then. Can I go now?</DIALOGUE>
        <DIALOGUE>~y~You~s~: You're free to go. Sorry for the delay.</DIALOGUE>
        <DIALOGUE>~o~Postman~s~: Next time maybe call ahead or something…</DIALOGUE>
    </D_AnnoyedPostman>
    <D_SuspectTalk>
        <DIALOGUE>~y~You~s~: Afternoon. I saw you leaving a property back there—mind telling me what you were doing?</DIALOGUE>
        <DIALOGUE>~o~Postman~s~: Just delivering a package, officer. I’m on my route.</DIALOGUE>
        <DIALOGUE>~y~You~s~: That’s strange, we’ve had several reports of packages going missing recently. Mind telling me the address?</DIALOGUE>
        <DIALOGUE>~o~Postman~s~: Uh… 142 Grove Street, I think? Just following orders.</DIALOGUE>
        <DIALOGUE>~y~You~s~: That house hasn’t had deliveries in weeks. Can I see some credentials?</DIALOGUE>
        <DIALOGUE>~o~Postman~s~: I… I think I left my badge at the warehouse. Look, it’s just a small job.</DIALOGUE>
        <DIALOGUE>~y~You~s~: Sounds more like theft. You need to step out of the vehicle.</DIALOGUE>
        <DIALOGUE>~o~Postman~s~: Alright, alright. No need to make a scene. I’ll cooperate.</DIALOGUE>
        <DIALOGUE>~y~You~s~: You’d better. You're coming with me.</DIALOGUE>
    </D_SuspectTalk>
    <D_SuspectPursuit>
        <DIALOGUE>~y~You~s~: Stop the vehicle and step out. I have some questions for you.</DIALOGUE>
        <DIALOGUE>~o~Postman~s~: I don’t think that’s necessary. I'm just doing my job, officer.</DIALOGUE>
        <DIALOGUE>~y~You~s~: You match the description of a suspect in multiple thefts. Shut off the engine.</DIALOGUE>
        <DIALOGUE>~o~Postman~s~: Yeah… not today!</DIALOGUE>
    </D_SuspectPursuit>
    <D_SuspectShooting>
        <DIALOGUE>~y~You~s~: Alright, out of the vehicle—hands where I can see them.</DIALOGUE>
        <DIALOGUE>~o~Postman~s~: Don’t come any closer, I swear to God!</DIALOGUE>
        <DIALOGUE>~y~You~s~: You’re impersonating a delivery driver and stealing packages. It’s over!</DIALOGUE>
        <DIALOGUE>~o~Postman~s~: You cops think you can control everything!</DIALOGUE>
        <DIALOGUE>~y~You~s~: Drop the weapon now!</DIALOGUE>
        <DIALOGUE>~o~Postman~s~: Not gonna happen!</DIALOGUE>
        <DIALOGUE>~y~You~s~: Last warning!</DIALOGUE>
        <DIALOGUE>~o~Postman~s~: I’m not going to prison!</DIALOGUE>
    </D_SuspectShooting>
    <D_SuspectSurrender>
        <DIALOGUE>~y~You~s~: Exit the vehicle now and keep your hands visible!</DIALOGUE>
        <DIALOGUE>~o~Postman~s~: Okay, okay! Don’t shoot!</DIALOGUE>
        <DIALOGUE>~y~You~s~: Down on your knees, now!</DIALOGUE>
        <DIALOGUE>~o~Postman~s~: Alright! I give up!</DIALOGUE>
        <DIALOGUE>~y~You~s~: You’re under arrest for package theft and impersonating a delivery worker.</DIALOGUE>
        <DIALOGUE>~o~Postman~s~: I didn’t mean for this to go that far…</DIALOGUE>
        <DIALOGUE>~y~You~s~: You’ll have a chance to explain it at the station.</DIALOGUE>
    </D_SuspectSurrender>
    <SCENARIOS>
        <THIEF>
            <TEXT>Keep an eye on the area. A delivery should happen soon.</TEXT>
            <TEXT>Perform a traffic stop to talk to the driver.</TEXT>
            <TEXT>Press ~y~{Y}~s~ to talk to the driver.</TEXT>
        </THIEF>
        <POSTMAN>
            <TEXT>Keep an eye on the area. A delivery should happen soon.</TEXT> <!--The same line as above-->
            <TEXT>Perform a traffic stop to talk to the driver.</TEXT> <!--The same line as above-->
            <TEXT>Press ~y~{Y}~s~ to talk to the driver.</TEXT> <!--The same line as above-->
            <TEXT>~g~The delivery appears legitimate. No further action is required.</TEXT>
        </POSTMAN>
    </SCENARIOS>
    <END>
        <TEXT>Package theft investigation concluded. Resume patrol.</TEXT>
        <TEXT>Looks like that's it. Continue your patrol.</TEXT>
        <TEXT>Nothing more to do here. Get back out there.</TEXT>
        <TEXT>~r~The Postman died</TEXT>
    </END>
</CALLOUT>