<CALLOUT>
    <CALLOUTMESSAGE>Traffic Accident</CALLOUTMESSAGE>
    <TASK>Multiple callers reporting at least one vehicle disabled, possible injuries.</TASK>
    <SCENARIO>
        <DRUNKHIGH>
            <DRIVER>
                <TEXT>~o~Driver:~s~ Hello, what's going oooon...</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~y~You:~s~ Hello, can you tell me what has happened?</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~o~Driver:~s~ I dunno, man... I was… I was just drivin'. Lights, screech — next thing I know we're here. I'm fine, I'm fine, really. Just a little dizzy.</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~y~You:~s~ Have you been drinking or taking anything?</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~o~Driver:~s~ Look, I don't wanna make trouble — yeah, I had a few. It's just a couple, honest. I can walk, I can talk. Keys? Uh—my bag's in the back. Sorry, officer, I don't mean no harm.</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~y~You:~s~ Do you remember what happened before the crash?</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~o~Driver:~s~ I — blur. Head spins. There was headlights, then metal... I remember the other car — oh god, are they okay? I didn't hit nobody on purpose.</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~y~You:~s~ Stay where you are. Don't move, I'm going to check on the other driver.</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~o~Driver:~s~ Yeah... please. Tell 'em I'm sorry. Tell 'em I'm real sorry...</TEXT>
            </DRIVER>
            <DRIVER2>
                <TEXT>~o~Driver2:~s~ ...ow... where... where am I?</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~y~You:~s~ You're at the scene of a collision. Can you tell me what happened?</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~o~Driver2:~s~ I... I don't remember. One moment I was driving, then — pain. My head feels fuzzy. I can't really see clearly. My left shoulder hurts. I don't know how it happened.</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~y~You:~s~ Do you know if anyone else was involved? Any other car or person?</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~o~Driver2:~s~ I... I heard a loud sound. There was braking... maybe another vehicle. I can't tell, I'm sorry. Could you call an ambulance? It hurts to move.</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~y~You:~s~ Help is on the way. Try to stay calm and still. Your name?</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~o~Driver2:~s~ It's... Please... don't let me bleed out...</TEXT>
            </DRIVER2>
        </DRUNKHIGH>
        <MEDICALEMERGENCY>
            <DRIVER>
                <TEXT>~o~Driver:~s~ Officer... I–I don’t feel good...</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~y~You:~s~ Try to stay calm. What happened?</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~o~Driver:~s~ I was driving... chest started burning... vision went blurry... I tried to pull over but... guess I didn’t make it.</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~y~You:~s~ Are you hurt anywhere else?</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~o~Driver:~s~ No... just this pressure... like someone’s sitting on my chest... please, I can’t breathe right.</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~y~You:~s~ Medical is here, they’ll take care of you. Don’t move more than you have to.</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~o~Driver:~s~ Thank you... just... don’t let me pass out.</TEXT>
            </DRIVER>
            <MEDIC>
                <TEXT>~r~Medic:~s~ Officer, we’ve got the patient. Symptoms look cardiac. We need space to work.</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~y~You:~s~ Understood. Anything you need from me?</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~r~Medic:~s~ Keep the traffic back and give us a few minutes. We’ll stabilize and transport.</TEXT>
            </MEDIC>
            <MEDIC2>
                <TEXT>~r~Medic2:~s~ BP is low, pulse irregular. Prepping oxygen.</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~y~You:~s~ Is the patient going to be okay?</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~r~Medic2:~s~ Too early to tell, but we’ve got it under control. Thanks for the quick response.</TEXT>
            </MEDIC2> 
        </MEDICALEMERGENCY>
        <TIREBURST>
            <DRIVER>
                <TEXT>~o~Driver:~s~ Officer! Thank god you’re here!</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~y~You:~s~ What happened?</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~o~Driver:~s~ My front tire just exploded out of nowhere! Car jerked sideways and I lost control.</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~y~You:~s~ Any injuries?</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~o~Driver:~s~ Just a few scratches and a bit shaken. Thought the whole car was gonna flip.</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~y~You:~s~ I will call an ambulance for you. Did you hit anything else?</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~o~Driver:~s~ Yes, I skidded into the guardrail and hit it. Scared the hell out of me.</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~y~You:~s~ Stay here while I check the vehicle. We might need a tow truck for it.</TEXT>
            </DRIVER>
        </TIREBURST>
        <FLATTIRE>
            <DRIVER>
                <TEXT>~o~Driver:~s~ Officer, sorry for the mess…</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~y~You:~s~ What seems to be the issue?</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~o~Driver:~s~ Front tire went flat while I was driving. Car started wobbling, so I braked hard and ended up stopping like this.</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~y~You:~s~ Anyone injured?</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~o~Driver:~s~ No, just annoyed. Could’ve been worse though.</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~y~You:~s~ Do you need roadside assistance?</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~o~Driver:~s~ Yeah… that’d be great. I’ve got no spare.</TEXT>
            </DRIVER>
        </FLATTIRE>
        <POWERFAILURE>
            <DRIVER>
                <TEXT>~o~Driver:~s~ That blackout came out of nowhere! Everything went dark!</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~y~You:~s~ Tell me what happened.</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~o~Driver:~s~ Streetlights died instantly. Couldn’t see a damn thing ahead of me. I tried to brake but I was already too close to the curb.</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~y~You:~s~ Any electrical issues with your car?</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~o~Driver:~s~ Yeah, the dashboard flickered right before I hit. Maybe the power surge messed with the car too.</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~y~You:~s~ Alright, stay put. I’ll check the area.</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~o~Driver:~s~ Please do. Feels like the whole city just switched off.</TEXT>
            </DRIVER>
        </POWERFAILURE>
        <SPEEDING>
            <DRIVER>
                <TEXT>~o~Driver:~s~ Officer, look — he braked way too hard! I had no time to react!</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~y~You:~s~ Were you speeding?</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~o~Driver:~s~ Maybe a little… traffic was light, I thought it was fine.</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~y~You:~s~ How fast were you going?</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~o~Driver:~s~ I… don’t know. Faster than I should’ve, okay?</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~y~You:~s~ Stay here while I check the other driver.</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~o~Driver:~s~ Just great… this day is ruined.</TEXT>
            </DRIVER>
            <DRIVER2>
                <TEXT>~o~Driver2:~s~ Officer! He was flying behind me! I checked my mirror and he was right on me!</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~y~You:~s~ Were you speeding as well?</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~o~Driver2:~s~ I was keeping with traffic! He came out of nowhere!</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~y~You:~s~ Do you need medical assistance?</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~o~Driver2:~s~ No, just rattled. But he needs to slow down before he kills someone.</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~y~You:~s~ I’ll talk to him. Stay here.</TEXT>
                <TEXT>~o~Driver2:~s~ Thanks. I just want my car intact...</TEXT>
            </DRIVER2>
        </SPEEDING>
    </SCENARIO>
</CALLOUT>