<BicycleAccident>

    <General>
        <Text>Bicycle traffic accident</Text>
        <Text>Analyse the scene</Text>
        <Text>And have you found out what caused this accident?</Text>
        <Text>Callout Bicycle Accident ended.</Text>
    </General>


    <D_Witness1_0>
        <Dialogue>Hi, my name is Greg. I tell you why this happened.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>See this suspect over there? He should be citated.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>He was driving too fast over the speed limit.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>People don't care about the speed limit these days.</Dialogue>
    </D_Witness1_0>

    <D_Witness2_0>
        <Dialogue>Hello. I saw a part of the accident.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>He was waiting on the sidewalk and looking back towards the oncoming vehicles.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>He had something in his hands, too. I couldn't see it.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>I'm not 100% sure and don't wanna blame the cyclist, but he looked nervous.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>Then I was minding my own business when I heard a loud boom, that was when it happened.</Dialogue>
    </D_Witness2_0>

    <D_Witness3_0>
        <Dialogue>My name is Paul, I am telling you, we need more protection for bicyclists.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>There is no bikeway, where should a bike rider safely drive then?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>But you can't blame the car driver, this bicyclist was just stupid.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>He looked to the right, right at the oncoming vehicle. That's when he started to ride.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>That's stupid, isn't it?</Dialogue>
    </D_Witness3_0>

    <D_Witness4_Driver_0>
        <Dialogue>Hello, I'm Sarah. I saw what happened while driving.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>The suspect was clearly up to something.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>Oh sorry, I should mention I'm talking about the bike rider.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>He had a camera in his hand, it looked like he wanted to film it.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>It looked like the cyclist wanted to jump right in front of the vehicle.</Dialogue>
    </D_Witness4_Driver_0>

    <D_Suspect_0>
        <Dialogue>Hello Officer, I'm sorry for all that.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>Was it the fault of the cyclist? Or mine? I haven't seen the biker at all.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>I was driving when suddenly the cyclist was right in front of me.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>I hit the brakes hard, but it wasn't enough. I hope he will be fine.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>My car is badly damaged, but the insurance will take care of that.</Dialogue>
    </D_Suspect_0>


    <D_Witness1_1>
        <Dialogue>Yo, why does this take so long?! I'm in a hurry.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>I'm on the way to work, I am already 5 minutes late!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>I only saw the biker drive like hell, way too fast.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>He was driving very fast on the sidewalk, that's what I saw.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>I really need to go now, bye!</Dialogue>
    </D_Witness1_1>

    <D_Witness2_1>
        <Dialogue>Hi, my name is Linda. These cyclists, always blocking the road!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>No wonder accidents like these happen. Drivers need to be fast at their destination and can't wait for riders.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>This bike rider wasn't even wearing a helmet! How negligent!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>This biker drove like hell. And all the other cars need to dangerously take over, risking the lives of the oncoming traffic!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>I'll tell you, you need to keep an eye on this cyclist.</Dialogue>
    </D_Witness2_1>

    <D_Witness3_1>
        <Dialogue>Hi, I am Paul. I would like to report. Wow, I really like your uniform.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>What kind of pistol are you carrying? Is it the SFP9? What a nice gun.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>Oh yeah, sorry, first of all I saw the biker wasn't carrying a helmet.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>Write down: The cyclist wore headphones and wasn't carrying a helmet while riding.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>Tell me, Do I have what it takes to be a police officer?</Dialogue>
    </D_Witness3_1>

    <D_Witness4_Driver_1>
        <Dialogue>Hello, I am Sarah. I drove towards the accident in the oncoming lane. I saw everything.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>The car was parked, then the driver was about to drive off.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>That's when the cyclist switched from sidewalk to the street, he wasn't even looking.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>The cyclist was driving fast. That's all what I saw.</Dialogue>
    </D_Witness4_Driver_1>


    <D_Suspect_1_2>
        <Dialogue>Hello, what a scene we have here. All because this biker cut me off.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>Stupid bikers, now look at my car! The front is screwed!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>I just bought this vehicle, it's not even a month old!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>The biker drove on the sidewalk, then suddenly drove into me. I had no chance to react.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>I hope he gets well soon, don't get me wrong. But I wasn't at fault.</Dialogue>
    </D_Suspect_1_2>

    <D_Witness1_2>
        <Dialogue>Yo, I'm in a hurry, make it quick. Listen.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>My name? It's Greg. I need to get to work fast.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>I only saw the car speeding, way too fast.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>I don't know anything about the bicycle, I didn't see it.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>Can I go now? That's all I know.</Dialogue>
    </D_Witness1_2>

    <D_Witness2_2>
        <Dialogue>Hey, my name is Linda. Man, look at that bicycle, completely screwed.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>I was watching the biker, because of the bicycle. That is or was... my favorite one.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>Oh sorry, he was driving on the side of the road. Suddenly he was hit from behind.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>I heard loud braking and then... the bicycle flew away...</Dialogue>
    </D_Witness2_2>

    <D_Witness3_2>
        <Dialogue>Oh hey Officer, I am Paul, nice to meet you!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>You know I was thinking about working on the force, I am made for it.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>I was walking when I saw this bike rider. He wasn't wearing a helmet and had no front bike light.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>Sometimes it's hard to see people with dark clothes, especially in bad weather conditions.</Dialogue>
    </D_Witness3_2>

    <D_Witness4_Driver_2>
        <Dialogue>Hi! My name is Sarah. I work in the bakery nearby.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>I was looking out the window when I saw a car driving by.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>It could have been speeding, but I saw him on his phone. I'm pretty sure it was this car.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>I ran outside when I heard the loud bang. That's when I saw the incident.</Dialogue>
    </D_Witness4_Driver_2>  


    <Persons>
        <Text>You</Text>
        <Text>Greg</Text>
        <Text>Linda</Text>
        <Text>Paul</Text>
        <Text>Sarah</Text>
        <Text>Paramedic</Text>
        <Text>Victim</Text>
        <Text>Peter</Text>
        <Text>Isabella</Text>
        <Text>Officer Thompson</Text>
        <Text>Officer Reynolds</Text>
        <Text>Officer Harrison</Text>
        <Text>Officer Clinton</Text>
        <Text>Firefighter</Text>
    </Persons>


    <D_Paramedic1>
        <Dialogue>Hey, how is it going? Don't get distracted from my big ass crowex watch for 10.000.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>Oh, how's the patient doing? The cyclist doesn't look good. He is badly injured.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>He is not responsive, so we need to take him to the hospital immediately.</Dialogue>
    </D_Paramedic1>

    <D_Paramedic2>
        <Dialogue>I don't have time to chat. The biker has some bad wounds, so please don't interrupt.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>* groans * ...</Dialogue>
    </D_Paramedic2>

    <D_Officer1>
        <Dialogue>Hey Officer! Thanks for showing up! We have some kind of traffic accident here.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>Feel free to interview the witnesses, I'll hang around here in the meantime.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>Find out who's at fault and what's even going on here. If you finished investigating, talk to me again! Good luck!</Dialogue>
    </D_Officer1>


    <D_Officer1_InsuranceFraud>
        <Dialogue>The cyclist attempted to commit insurance fraud against the driver.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>As soon as he is cleared by medical we will arrest him! Thanks so far!</Dialogue>
    </D_Officer1_InsuranceFraud>

    <D_Officer1_BikersFault>
        <Dialogue>The cyclist clearly didn't focus on the road. It's his fault.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>Alright, as soon as he is cleared by medical he will get a fine! Thank you!</Dialogue>
    </D_Officer1_BikersFault>

    <D_Officer1_DriversFault>
        <Dialogue>The driver clearly didn't follow traffic laws. He is to blame!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>Understood, arrest the driver!</Dialogue>
    </D_Officer1_DriversFault>


    <D_Officer2>
        <Dialogue>I haven't had my morning coffee, our machine is broken...</Dialogue>
    </D_Officer2>

    <D_Officer3>
        <Dialogue>Hey, this person saw something, you might talk to them.</Dialogue>
    </D_Officer3>

    <D_Officer4>
        <Dialogue>Hi partner, what a bad accident. Make sure to interview all witnesses.</Dialogue>
    </D_Officer4>

    <D_Fireman1>
        <Dialogue>This vehicle has bad front damage.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>We're just here in case the vehicle burns or looses oil.</Dialogue>
    </D_Fireman1>

    <D_Fireman3>
        <Dialogue>Man, I love coffee from Bean Machine, especially in the night shifts. You should try it!</Dialogue>
    </D_Fireman3>


    <Menu>
        <Text>Scenario</Text>
        <Text>Traffic Accident</Text>
        <Text>Choose the right one!</Text>

        <Text>Insurance Fraud</Text>
        <Text>The cyclist did it on purpose!</Text>
        <Text>The cyclist attempted Insurance Fraud!</Text>

        <Text>Bikers Fault</Text>
        <Text>The biker didn't pay attention!</Text>
        <Text>It's the cyclists fault!</Text>

        <Text>Drivers Fault</Text>
        <Text>The driver is at fault!</Text>
        <Text>The car driver caused the accident!</Text>

        <Text>~g~Investigation correct</Text>
        <Text>~r~Investigation failed</Text>

        <Text>Press ~y~End~s~ anytime to end the callout.</Text>
    </Menu>

</BicycleAccident>