<BurningDumpster>

    <General>
        <Text>~r~Burning dumpster~b~ reported</Text>
        <Text>Unit with fire extinguisher respond Code 2</Text>
        <Text>Drive to the location and extinguish the ~r~fire~s~ or call the ~r~fire department!</Text>
    </General>

    <Persons>
        <Text>Caller</Text>
        <Text>You</Text>
    </Persons>

    <Extingiush>
        <Text>To get a ~r~fire extinguisher~s~, go to your trunk and press</Text>
        <Text>~r~Fire extinguisher~s~ equipped!</Text>
        <Text>Now search for ~y~evidence~s~ by pressing {Key} while in the ~y~markers~s~.</Text>
    </Extingiush>

    <Tasks>
        <Text>Talk to the 911 ~b~caller~s~ with</Text>
        <Text>Press {MusicMenuKey} anytime to view the picture again!</Text>
        <Text>Dispatch, Suspect is ~r~fleeing!</Text>
    </Tasks>

    <Caller>
        <Dialogue>Hello, are you the one who reported the burning trash?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>Yes, that was me. I wanted to report a suspicious person I saw.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>I was walking past the trash can when I saw someone walking away.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>Right after that the fire started!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>This sounds suspicious. Do you have details about the suspect?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>Sure, it was a {gender} and around {age} years old.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>I even managed to take a photo. Here it is!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>Thanks. We're looking for the suspect now. Goodbye!</Dialogue>
    </Caller>

    <Genders>
        <Text>female</Text>
        <Text>male</Text>
        <Text>non-binary</Text>
    </Genders>

    <Evidence>
        <Dialogue>A Molotov cocktail, this was no accident... someone wanted to start a fire.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>A jerrycan full of gasoline, looks like someone was preparing to ignite something.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>A bong? Strange... maybe someone was too high to notice the fire they started.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>A frag grenade. This is no simple fire, we're dealing with something far more dangerous.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>A smoke grenade. Could have been used to cover up their tracks before setting the fire.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>A broken bottle. It seems improvised, but it could have been used to start the fire.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>A gas cylinder. If this went off, the whole area could've gone up in flames.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>An oil drum. It's leaking... and highly flammable. Looks like someone wanted to spread the fire.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>A petrol can. Smells like gasoline... someone really wanted to burn this place down.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>A sock? Well, it might not seem like much, but it smells bad enough to be a fire hazard.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>Typical. Somebody threw a burning cigarette in the trash, then it started igniting.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>A sock? Well, it might not seem like much, but it smells bad enough to be a fire hazard.</Dialogue>
    </Evidence>

    <End>
        <Text>~g~Situation is Code 4.</Text>
    </End>
    
</BurningDumpster>