<ConvenienceStoreDispute>

    <General>
        <Text>Convenience Store Dispute</Text>
        <Text>Solve the discrepancy</Text>
    </General>

    <Persons>
        <Text>~y~You:~s~ </Text>
        <Text>~HC_7~Lady:~s~ </Text>
        <Text>~b~Clerk:~s~ </Text>
    </Persons>

    <D_Argue>
        <Dialogue>Officer! The clerk doesn't want to take my coupon!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>M'am, I already told you, this coupon is invalid. I can't accept it.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>That's ridicolous, it's valid! I do have rights! You can't refuse to take it!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>Officer, may you please take a look at it and clarify?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>Sure, let me see it...</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>* Looks at coupon... *</Dialogue>
    </D_Argue>

    <D_Expired>
        <Dialogue>* Coupon for 30 $ at 24/7 market, expires on 06/01/2024 *</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>The coupon is definitely expired.</Dialogue>
    </D_Expired>

    <D_Manipulated>
        <Dialogue>* You can see the 24/7 market coupon for 30$ is manipulated to 60 $ *</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>This coupon has been manipulated. Look, the numbers were changed.</Dialogue>
    </D_Manipulated>

    <D_RefuseLeave>
        <Dialogue>This can't be real! You're lying!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>Officer, that's racist! I won't go before I receive my right!</Dialogue>
    </D_RefuseLeave>

    <D_Run>
        <Dialogue>Everybody is against me! Forget it, I won't pay this!</Dialogue>
    </D_Run>

    <D_Fight>
        <Dialogue>I have enough of your bullshit!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>And you Officer, are part of the problem!!! Aaaaaargh!</Dialogue>
    </D_Fight>

    <D_Taser>
        <Dialogue>How dare you threaten me!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>ASSAULT! You have attacked me!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>This is self-defense!</Dialogue>
    </D_Taser>



    <D_Eco_Argue>
        <Dialogue>This is outrageous! Look at this packaging! Plastic everywhere! Are you trying to kill the planet?</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>Ma'am, I understand your concern, but we don't manufacture the products. We just sell them.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>Just sell them? So you're complicit! Selling non-eco-friendly products is basically illegal!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>Ma'am, that's not true. There are no laws against this packaging—</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>Don't lie to me! I'll have this store shut down for engaging in illegal activities! You're part of the problem! You're a—you're a murderer!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>Excuse me? Alright Officer, please remove her from the store and M'am, you're banned from this store from now on.</Dialogue>
    </D_Eco_Argue>

    <D_Eco_RefuseLeave>
        <Dialogue>I will not leave this store until this criminal is arrested!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>Ma'am, I understand you're upset, but this is not a criminal matter. You need to leave the store, or I'll have to remove you myself.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>I refuse! If you don't arrest this murderer, then YOU'RE complicit too! I'll stay here all day if I have to!</Dialogue>
    </D_Eco_RefuseLeave>

    <D_Eco_FleeWPackage>
        <Dialogue>You know what? If you won't fix it, I'll do it myself! This ends now!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>I'm saving the planet! This belongs in proper disposal, not on your filthy shelves!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>Ma'am, that's theft. Put the item down and step away.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>It's not theft if I'm saving humanity! Arrest THEM for stocking this garbage!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>Ma'am, this is your last warning. Drop the item and cooperate, or you'll be placed under arrest.</Dialogue>
    </D_Eco_FleeWPackage>

    <D_Eco_Argumentative>
        <Dialogue>Officer! You need to arrest this man immediately! He's a murderer! Selling all this plastic — he's practically choking the Earth himself!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>Ma'am, this isn't a criminal matter. Now, if you—</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>Don't even start with me! Where's your supervisor? I want their name. And YOU— * pointing at the officer * —I want your name and badge number! RIGHT NOW!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>Ma'am, we're not doing this. Either leave the store, or I'll have to escort you out.</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>Oh, I'd love to see you try! I'm going to report ALL of you! Corporate, the mayor, the media—everyone will hear about this!</Dialogue>
    </D_Eco_Argumentative>

    <D_Eco_Taser>
        <Dialogue>Oh, so now you're threatening me? I feel so unsafe right now! This is assault!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>Ma'am, no one is threatening you. Please calm—</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>ASSAULT! YOU ASSAULTED ME! Everyone saw it!</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>Ma'am, no one has touched you. Let's just—</Dialogue>
        <Dialogue>Don't you talk to me, murderer!</Dialogue>
    </D_Eco_Taser>



    <End>
        <Text>Callout is Code 4.</Text>
    </End>

</ConvenienceStoreDispute>
